RobertJ. Cistone

Assistant Chief Engineer

Crum Lynne, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/RobertJ-Cistone/a7b801ad80295367

To secure a challenge position in the electrical or machining field that offers job security and growth potential.

20 years' experience in electrical industry-Residential/ Commercial

6 year experience in machining- 3 yrs CNC, 3 yrs engine

lathes/ bridge ports operator

Motivated, independent and driven.

Maintains excellent interpersonal communication, works well independently and able to supervise others, provides cost effective time management and problem resolution skills.

Clean driving record with no violations.

TWIC Card

American Home Fire Safety, NFPA Certified as an independent fire safety consultant

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Chief Engineer

Renaissance Hotel - Essington, PA - May 2012 to February 2013

Responsibilities include major renovations; maintain electrical, plumbing, HVAC, and other construction structures. Servicing guest rooms

Start as Maintenance Supervisor end as Assistant chief

Ramada Inn - Essington, PA - April 2011 to May 2012

Engineer

Responsibilities include major renovations; maintain electrical, plumbing, HVAC, and other construction structures. Servicing guest rooms

Machinist

Chambers & Kubeck Inc - Aston, PA - January 2006 to February 2010

Responsibilities included, fabricating metals, repairing

valves and pumps. Additional required machining tasks on-site at power plant facilities throughout the country.

CNC Machine Operator

Thyssen Krupp Inc - Aston, PA - September 2003 to October 2005

Responsibilities included getting up machines for operation and using computer systems to maintain equipment.

Electrician- Assistant Supervisor

Watson Electric - Wilson, NC - July 1993 to July 2003

Responsibilities included wiring residential dwellings, renovating electrical systems to comply with codes, troubleshooting and performing customer service.

Electrician- Assistant Supervisor

David Simmons Electric - Goldsboro, NC - April 2000 to March 2002

Responsibilities included renovations of military housing on base including but not limited to complete panel upgrades,

upgrading of devices and light fixtures.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Electrical Technology

Ocean City High School - Ocean City, NJ 1992